Charlie Nelms papers, 1967-2016 C701
Indiana University Archives
- Speeches, 1967-2016
  - Prerequisites for Diversifying the Academic, April 17, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Jimmy Ross Memorial Service, May 28, 2002 (Box 3)
  - IU Foundation Board Showalter House, June 14, 2002 (Box 3)
  - ACE Marginalization in the Academy Conference, June 29, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Address to IU Football Players, August 8, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Prerequisites for Leadership, NMBCC, September 7, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal Officer Development Series Opening Dinner, September 10, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Brother's Keeper, September 17, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Pastor Tillman Appreciation, Memphis, TN, October 12-13, 2002 (Box 3)
  - NAACP Freedom Fund Banquet, October 19, 2002 (Box 3)
  - WGCL Interview, December 5, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Why Diversity is Everyone's Business, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Northside Exchange Club, Jimmy Ross Endowment Fund Check Presentation, January 8, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Supporting Diversity, School of HPER, January 17, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Board of Trustees Conversation, January 31, 2003 (Box 3)
  - NRHH Keynote Speaker, February 2, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Annual Ethnic Buffet, Muncie, Indiana, February 22, 2003 (Box 3)
  - University of Southern Indiana Sydney Berger Lecture, March 27, 2003 (Box 3)
  - University of Evansville Alumni Association Keynote Speaker, March 29, 2003 (Box 3)
  - IUPUI Honors Convocation, April 4, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Neal-Marshall Black Identity Series, Lessons Taught and Lessons Learned, April 24, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Some Unsolicited Advice on the Occasion of Commencing a New Journey, Ivy Tech Commencement, May 16, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Beyond the Rhetoric: Prerequisites for Diversifying the Academy, May 29, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Avoiding the Search Trap, June 16, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Prerequisites for Student Success, Central State University, August 29, 2003 (Box 3)
  - National Access to Success Conference, September 5, 2003 (Box 3)
  - ASDV Fall Reception, September 11, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Introduction to Lawrence Weekly, ICP Conference-IUPUI, October 18, 2003 (Box 3)
  - CASA Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, October 22-23, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall Meeting, South Bend, Indiana, November 6, 2003 (Box 3)
  - American Democracy Project, Enhancing Minority Attainment, November 12-14, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Loose speeches, 2004-2010; 3 Folders (Box 3)
  - Guest Speaker MLK Program, Columbus, Indiana, January 17, 2004 (Box 3)
  - African American History Month, Richmond, Indiana, February 10, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IPAS Conference, February 11, 2004 (Box 3)
  - National Conference of Minority Public Administrators, March 4-5, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Spring 2004 Neal Marshall Public Policy Lecture-Cora Breckenridge, March 22, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Prerequisites for Diversity, IU Southeast, March 25, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Welcome-Minority Faculty Hiring and Retention Workshop, April 9, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Indiana Pathways to College Network, April 23, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IUN Black Grads Reception, May 3, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Keynote Speaker, NAACP Life Membership Campaign and Awards Dinner, May 14, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IU Alumni Club of Dearborn County, May 17, 2004 (Box 3)
  - College Connection Luncheon, May 19, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IU South Bend, May 28, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Improving Higher Education Through Distance Learning, Colloquium and Consultation, Accra, Ghana, May 29-June 7, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Information on Presentation, Colloquium and Consultation, Accra, Ghana, May 29-June 7, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Colloquium/Consultation with Ghana Public Services Commission, Accra, Ghana, June 1-6, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IU Alumni Association Executive Council Mission Differentiation Presentation, June 18, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Millennium Leadership Institute, June 26-29, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal Officer Development Series Dinner, September 14, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Patterson Research Conference, September 24-27, 2004 (Box 3)
  - U544: Introduction to Student Affairs, September 28, 2004 (Box 3)
  - HOPE Foundation Open House, October 2, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Black Alumni Weekend, October 8-10, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Richmond, Indiana, October 16, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Enhancing Minority Attainment Conference, October 21-22, 2004 (Box 4)
  - The Race is On, NAACP State Convention Awards Banquet, October 23, 2004 (Box 4)
  - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff Homecoming, October 28-31, 2004 (Box 4)
  - 2004 Assessment Institute Presentation, November 1, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Role of the Contemporary Black Culture Center in Higher Education, American Association of Black Culture Centers Conference, November 5, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Closing Remarks, MLK Brunch, IMU Alumni Hall, January 16, 2005 (Box 4)
  - MLK Remarks, Fairview Elementary School, January 21, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Speak to Me, University of Southern Indiana, February 21, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Closing Remarks, AfricanaFest, Alumni Hall, February 26, 2005; 2 Folders (Box 4)
  - Black History Month Closing Reception, February 28, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Institutional Development and Student Affairs Staff Luncheon, March 8, 2005 (Box 4)
  - IU First Nations Pow Wow, April 1, 2005 (Box 4)
  - American College Personnel Association Presentation, Nashville, Tennessee, April 4, 2005; 2 Folders (Box 4)
  - College is Possible: Expanding College Access through Promising Practices, April 7-8, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Retention Conference, Communications Complex, IUPUI, April 8, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Annual Symposium Highlighting the Research of Faculty, Staff, and Students of Color, IUPUI, April 15, 2005 (Box 4)
  - University Conference on Diversity, University Place Conference Center, April 22, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Black Congratulatory Ceremony, Lee Norvell Theater and Drama Center, May 6, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Speaking engagements, 2007-2010 (Box 4)
  - Men's Day, Mt. Gilead Baptist Church, June 30, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Installation Address, North Carolina Central University, February 22, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Engaging the World Anew, HBCU Town Hall Meeting, September 20, 2011 (Box 4)
  - Loose speeches, 2013-2016 (Box 4)
  - Beyond the Rhetoric: Increasing College Access and Success for Minority Males, March 1, 2013 (Box 4)
  - The Prerequisites for Student Success, Dillard University, August 15, 2013 (Box 4)
  - Higher Purpose, Higher Expectations, Higher Outcomes, Jackson State University, August 16, 2013 (Box 4)
  - Important Lessons from my Leadership Journey, Neal-Marshall Kentuckiana Chapter, August 17, 2013 (Box 4)
  - Succeed Against All Odds, Richmond Minority Women's Network, August 22, 2013 (Box 4)
  - SEF Convening, December 5, 2013 (Box 4)
  - A Prayer for Courage, undated (Box 4)
- Indiana University East, 1987-1995
  Contains files from Nelms' tenure as Chancellor and Professor of Education at IU East in Richmond, Indiana, including official reports, correspondence, subject files, mementos, and media clippings.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Appointment letter, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Book chapter On the Outside Looking In, ed. William Harvey, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Center on Philanthropy scholar-in-residence update, 1993 (Box 4)
  - College Board, February 19, 1990; 2 Folders (Box 4)
  - Commencement speeches, 1990-1992 (Box 4)
  - Cultural Literacy, October 4, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Departure from IU East, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Diversity, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Earlham and IU East banners, undated (Box 4)
  - Graduating Class Council Dinner, April 30, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Honorary degree, Earlham College, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Increasing the Enrollment of African American Students, IUSB, February 8, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Increasing the Pool of Black College Graduates, 1990; 2 Folders (Box 4)
  - Indiana University East, 1988-1994; 2 Folders (Box 4)
  - Japan trip, 1990-1991; 2 Folders (Box 4)
  - Japan trip photo album, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Letter of Intent to Purdue, undated (Box 4)
  - Media, 1992-1994 (Box 4)
  - Media, Newspaper clippings, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Multicultural Workshop, June, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Nelms Reception, October 28, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Projects and reports, 1987-1995 (Box 4)
  - Race in America in the 21st Century: A Campus Dialogue, IU East, November 6, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Reflections, undated (Box 4)
  - Reports, 1987-1992 (Box 4)
  - Richmond-Wayne County Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Salary letter, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Plan, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Student Life Banquet, May 1, 1989 (Box 4)
- Indiana University Bloomington, 1992-2007
  Contains files from Nelms' tenure as Vice President for Institutional Development and Student Affairs at IU, including correspondence, reports, and subject files.
  - 20/20 Emails, 1998 (Box 4)
  - 20/20 Implementation Plan, 1998 (Box 4)
  - 20/20 Plan, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Appointment Letter, Center on Diversity, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Articles (University of Michigan-Flint departure, Indiana University Bloomington appointment), 1998 (Box 8)
  - Black Cultural Center-Diversity, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Congratulatory emails (leaving IU for NCCU), 2007; 2 Folders (Box 4)
  - Publications, 1999-2004 (Box 6)
  - Reports, Student Development and Diversity, 1999-2006 (Box 6)
  - Retention Coordinators Meeting, December 12, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Review Team, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Review team for diversity reorganization, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Review Team Report, June 20, 2005 (Box 6)
- Other Institutions, 1973-2016
  Covers Nelms' professional engagement with other, mostly academic, institutions. Contents include files from Nelms' tenure at Indiana University Northwest, Sinclair Community College, as well as his graduate education at Indiana University. Of special interest are files from Nelms' tenure as Chancellor at North Carolina Central University.
  - Africare, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Northwest, 1980-1993 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Northwest - Promotion and tenure dossier, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Northwest - Promotion and tenure dossier, loose items, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Northwest - Psychology in Teaching (P510), 1982 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Northwest - tenure file, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Northwest, Student Services Division Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Southeast, Board of Trustees Presentation on Student Success and Student Retention, September 14, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University Southeast, Faculty remarks, March 5, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Indiana University, teaching and education, 1976 (Box 6)
  - NCCU Now, 2010-2013 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Central Association, 1996-1998; 2 Folders (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Central University - Correspondence and remarks, 2010-2011 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Central University - Inaugural Address, 2008 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Central University – Notes, 2007-2012 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Central University – Publications, 2010-2013 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Central University – Publications, 2007-2010 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Central University – Reports, 2007-2010 (Box 6)
  - Open University Worldwide, 1998 (Box 6)
  - The Open University, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Placing the Unskilled-Semi-Skilled Worker, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Sinclair Community College, 1983-1985 (Box 6)
  - University of South Carolina-Spartenburg, 1993 (Box 6)
- Professional Activities, 1981-2017
  Covers Nelms' professional activities with regional and national organizations, commissions, and projects. Files include awards, event programs, correspondence, notes and remarks, and publications.
  - Middle Central Association of Colleges and Schools evaluation and assessment files, 1997-2000 (Box 6)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1995-1998; 4 Folders (Box 6)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities publications, 1991-2008 (Box 6)
  - African American Pioneer Awards/Forum Magazine, Now is the Time, February 1, 1996 (Box 6)
  - African American Presidents and Chancellors, undated (Box 7)
  - African Americans and college publications, 1996-2009 (Box 7)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1981 (Box 7)
  - American Association of Blacks in Higher Education, undated (Box 7)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities Annual Meeting, November 18-22, 1995 (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education, 1981-2010 (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education Commission on Leadership Development, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education Commission on Leadership Development, September 22-23, 1998 (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education Commission on Leadership Development, April 4, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Black Male conference at IPFW, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Black Male Summit at Claflin University, undated (Box 7)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Evaluating Student Performance Workshop, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Evaluation of the Gary Community School Corporation Labor Market Orientation Program, undated (Box 7)
  - Federal Reserve Bank, Lumina Travel, undated (Box 7)
  - Formula for Personal Success, 1986 (Box 7)
  - HBCU Week Conference, September 26-27, 2013 (Box 7)
  - HBCU Work, 2010-2013 (Box 7)
  - Indiana University Distinguished Alumni Service Award, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Letters of Reference, A-C, undated (Box 7)
  - Letters of Reference, D-L, undated (Box 7)
  - Letters of Reference, M-Z, undated (Box 7)
  - Loose awards, 1998-2007 (Box 7)
  - Loose event programs, 1982-2017; 2 Folders (Box 7)
  - Loose publications and correspondence, 1980-2007 (Box 7)
  - Macau Trip, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Middle States Association Accreditation Visit, CUNY- Medgar Edgars College, March 9-12, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Middle States Association Commission on Higher Education, CUNY- Medgar Edgars College, June 4, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Middle States Association Evaluation, University of the District of Columbia, March 26-29, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Negro Educational Review, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - North Central Association, 1996-1998 (Box 7)
  - North Central Association Focused Visit-Central State University, Wilberforce, Ohio, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Presidents' Higher Education Community Service Honor Roll, 2010 (Box 7)
  - Writing Renewal Project, 1987 (Box 7)
- Personal, 1971-2016
  Contains files related to Nelms' educational background, family, and research. Includes family correspondence, publications, mementos such as buttons and badges, and media clippings.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Educational background-Indiana University, 1971-1978 (Box 7)
  - The Report of the President's Commission on Campus Unrest, including the detailed reports on the killings at Kent State and Jackson State, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Value Tree, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Journals, publications, and articles, 1978-1983; 2 Folders (Box 8)
  - Photographs, 1978-1993 (Box 8)
  - Planners and contacts, 1979-1996 (Box 9)
  - Loose mementos, 1980-1989 (Box 8)
  - Publications, 1981-1986 (Box 8)
  - Racism and Unliberated Negroes statements, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Philanthropic contributions, 1984-2011; 2 Folders (Box 8)
  - Invitation to Ronald Reagan rally, Dayton, Ohio, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Mementos, 1986-2014; 4 Folders (Box 8)
  - IU Alumni Magazine, 1987-1999 (Box 8)
  - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff Founder's Day Convocation, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Personal files, 1989-2004 (Box 8)
  - Affirmative Action in the '90s, 1990-1999 (Box 8)
  - Publications, 1990-1997 (Box 8)
  - McNeil High School Reunion, May 22-25, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Articles and mementos, 1994-1997 (Box 8)
  - Clippings and biographical, 1994-2004 (Box 8)
  - Personal files, 1994-2013 (Box 8)
  - Certificates, 1994; 2 Folders (Box 8)
  - Mementos (paper), 1994 (Box 8)
  - Nelms Scholarship, 1995-1998 (Box 8)
  - Charlie's Book notes, 1998-2001 (Box 8)
  - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, 1999/2017 (Box 8)
  - Family Reunion, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Neal Marshall Alumni Directory, 2002 (Box 8)
  - Publications, 2002-2016 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence and family, 2003-2011 (Box 10)
  - Start Where You Find Yourself: Lessons Taught and Lessons Learned by Charlie Nelms, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Invitation to Barack Obama inauguration, 2013 (Box 10)
  - Memoir file, 2016 (Box 10)
  - Newspapers and oversize materials, 1971-2016 (Box 11)
- Audiovisual, 1979-2011
  The Audiovisual series contains audiovisual material including videotapes, DVD's, audio cassettes, and one vinyl 45 RPM record. Titles include lectures and educational programs.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - 69th Annual American Council on Education Meeting, America Beyond the Horizon, Honorable H. Thomas Kean, Governor of New Jersey, genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - A Public Reception for Dr. Charlie Nelms and Family, Golden Leaf Neighborhood Service: Guest Speaker Dr. Charlie Nelms-Chancellor of UM-Flint, September 15, 1994- February 8, 1998; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - 1995- Black History Month Spots & Short documentary on Abortion, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Online Streaming in Media Collections Online
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/v405st62r. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    General
    Previous title: Black History Month Spots
  - Career Development Workshop, genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Career Development Workshop, January 25, 1979; genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Chancellor Nelms Interview, WJRT, 1995; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/h128nx88w. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: Chancellor Nelms Interview, WJRT
  - Charlie Nelms, Urban Perspective 432, June 21, 1998; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/8s45qs97f. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
  - Creole Ballads & Zydeco, Sybil Kein and Charles Moore, 1996; genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - D "Hooks", genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Dean's Dialog: "Listening to the Heart of Durham," A Conversation Between Sam Wells and Charlie Nelms, September 18, 2010; genreform: DVD (Box 11)
  - Donahue "Discrimination Among Blacks (Color)", genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/2227n638t. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: Donahue, "Discrimination Among Blacks (Color)"; alternate title Donahue "Blacks Discriminating Against Darker Blacks"
  - Dr. Charlie Nelms, UMF Chancellor-Interview on WJRT/12 by Norma Hall, April 14, 1996; 3 videotapes; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - Educational Opportunity & Initiatives recorded on 7-19-96, July 19, 1996; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/6t054018p. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: Educational Opportunity Initiatives
  - Family Road - Hutzel Hospital Spot, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/n583zc42v. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous Title: Family Road
  - Great Moments of the Indianapolis 500, June 28, 1997; genreform: DVD (Box 11)
  - Indiana University College Preparatory Initiatives, Parent Video Premiere- SOAR HIGHER: How you can make college a part of your child's future, July 27, 2000; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - Internet in the Classroom, Pt. 2, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/6h441928x. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
  - "Justice" Production, The Urban League Song by Ernest Ferrell, genreform: Vinyl Disc, 7" (Box 11)
  - 1989 MLK, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - Kaleidoscope, College Presidents, September 17, 1997; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - KPMG Peat Marwick's 21st Century University Conference, "The Future of Higher Education," J. Morley, June 18, 1997; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - Major Taylor, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - Mobilizing the Campus for Student Retention Pt. 2, American Association for Higher Education, 1982; genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Morning Edition, National Public Radio, September 15, 1995; genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - N.B.D. Presentation By C. Nelms, October 1997; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/tx31r167h. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: NBD Presentation
  - Networking Blacks in Higher Ed., with Blacks on White Campuses, genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Pro & Con #701 - Racism: What Can the U.S. & South Africa Learn From Each Other, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - Providing Access to Disabled Students, American Association for Higher Education, 1982; genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Quality Control and the Chief Academic Officer, genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Quality in Education-What Is It?, genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Racism 101, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - CAUSE: Seeing Higher Education in the Year 2020, 1994; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/0p096q973. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: Seeing Higher Education in the Year 2020, CAUSE93 Current Issues Forum
  - Shattering the Silences, Minority Professors Break Into the Ivory Tower, by Stanley Nelson and Gail Pellett, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - Southern Education Foundation HBCU Governance and Institutional Effectiveness Seminar, 2011; genreform: DVD (Box 11)
  - Purdue University Calumet Promotional Videos: 1.Student Recruitment 2. Community Relations, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/v118rx00h. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: Student Recruitment, Community Relations, AV/90
  - Tonya Frantico Interview WJRT, October 19, 1997; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/4q77g811v. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous titles: Sunday, WJRT Coverage, Tonya Frantico interview; CN- 10-19-97 WJRT Tonya Frantico Interview, October 19, 1997
  - Testing Workshop, April, 1981; genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - The Africans: A Triple Heritage, Episodes 6 through 9, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/ms35tt14n. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: The Africans
  - The Forum Magazine Presents the 7th Annual African American Pioneer Awards, February 2, 1997; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming acess for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/cn69mm71b. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
  - Top Secret "Mission Impossible", genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - U of M Janis, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/gf06gm477. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
  - Untitled audiocassettes, 2 Cassettes; genreform: Compact Cassette (Box 11)
  - Untitled videotapes, 2 videotapes; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - West Virginia University, Social Justice, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
  - University of Michigan-Flint Chancellor's Inauguration, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/9c67x4357. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.